Back in all my things for the summer
Lying on my bed, it's a bummer
Cause I didn't call when I got your number
But I liked you a lot
Slipping on my dress and soft filters
Everybody said you're a killer
But I couldn't stop the way I was feeling
The day your record dropped
The day I saw your white Mustang
Your white Mustang
Caught up in my dreams and forgetting
I've been acting like I'm a kid
Cause you held me in your arms
Just a little too tight
That's what I thought
Summer's meant for loving and leaving
I was such a fool for believing
That you could change all the ways
You've been living but you just
Couldn't stop
The day I saw your white Mustang
Your white Mustang
And you were revving it, revving it, revving it up
And the sun, it was bright now
And you were getting all bad about it
And you're the only one in town
You could see the light
You can see the light
You can see it
And you could see it
And you could see the light
You're gonna hear me like lightning
White Mustang
Your white Mustang
The day I saw your white Mustang
Said you're a white Mustang
Like lightning
You're gonna hear me
Oh death
Won't you spare me over another
But what is this that I can't see
With eyes full of
And taking hold of me
When God is gone
And the devil takes hold
Who'll have mercy
On your soul
Oh death
No wealth, no ruin, no silver, no gold
Nothing satisfies me but your soul
Oh death
Well I am death, none can excel
I'll open the door to heaven or hell
Oh death
Oh, Dad
My name is Dad
And the enemy is here
Never really felt bad about it
As we drank deep from the light
Cause I felt melting magnets, babe
The second I saw you through half-shut eyes
Smoking sunset off Mulhall and he was talking
I was wondering about you and that girl
She your girl
Girlfriend, face from heaven
Bet the world she don't know
Pretty girls don't know the things that I know
Bought my way out, shared the things that she won't
Uh-oh, dancing past the point of no return
Let's go, we can free ourselves of all we've learned
I love the secret language that we're speaking
Say it
Say it to me
Let's embrace the point of no return
Never really thought we would make it
We'd be thinking about what could've been
But we've had a record
Summer can't turn it down
Oh, now I don't wanna see the end begin
Smoking sunset off Mulhall and he was talking
I was wondering about you and that girl
She your girl
Girlfriend, face from heaven
Bet the world she don't know
Pretty girls don't know the things that I know
Bought my way out, shared the things that she won't
Uh-oh, dancing past the point of no return
Let's go, we can free ourselves of all we've learned
I love the secret language that we're speaking
Say it to me
Let's embrace the point of no return
Thank you for watching.
I want you to fall into this world
Floating in the sky
Singing the song I want to sing
Hurry and destroy me
I want you to fall into this world
Floating in the sky
Singing the song I want to sing
I want you
I want you to fall into this world
Floating in the sky
Singing the song I want to sing
I want you to fall into this world
Floating in the sky
Singing the song I want to sing
Floating in this world
Floating in the sky
全荒野 全荒野 全荒野 全荒野
A couple rebel top gun pilots flyin' with no where to be
Don't know you super well, but I think that you might be the same as me
Behave abnormally
Let's let things come out of the woodwork
I'll give you my best, I'll tell you all my best lies
Yeah, awesome, right?
So let's let things come out of the woodwork
I'll give you my best, I'll tell you all my best lies
See me rollin', showin' someone else love
Dancin' with our shoes off, no, I think you're awesome, right?
Our rules, our dreams, we're blind
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night
Get your friend to drive, but he can hardly see
We'll end up painted on the road
Red and chrome, all the broken glass sparkly
I guess we're partying
So let's let things come out of the woodwork
I'll give you my best, I'll tell you all my best lies
See me rollin', showin' someone else love
Dancin' with our shoes off, no, I think you're awesome, right?
Our rules, our dreams, we're blind
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-to the night of friends
Our drinks, we get inspired
Blown shit up with homemade
To-to-to-dynamite
Our friends, our drinks
We get inspired
Don't shit up with a homie
To-to-to-dynamite
Our rules, our dreams
We're blind
Don't shit up with a homie
To-to-to-dynamite
Our friends, our drinks
We get inspired
Don't shit up with a homie
To-to-to-dynamite
Let's ride
when the wind is blowing
To-to-do-to-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do
When I was born
I lived
on Poplar Street
Just a little child
With plans
Just on my knees
Watchin home run
from the
up in the trees
I saw Mrs. Monsley Brown
with Mr. Keats
I feel like a human
Graves, I was in my bed
Please drink to the crisp end
Graves, I was in the sand
I am a true romantic
Free-falling, I'm acting
Mama always called that woman
Prostitutes wearing lowered cuffs
Stained bones and red lipstick
And red lipstick and red lipstick
One night Mrs. Monsley made
Her eyes in me
Pulled me to her door
Ain't stuck her teeth in deep
I feel like a human
Graves, I was in my bed
Please drink to the crisp end
Graves, I was in the sand
I feel like a human
Graves, I was in my bed
Please drink to the crisp end
I am a true romantic
Free-falling, I'm acting
All your days are gone
Sitting on the floor
In your underwear
Begging me for more
And all my days are gone
Sitting on the floor
In my underwear
Begging you for more
I am a true romantic
Free-falling, I'm acting
Yeah
On Poplar Street
Tangled up in love
Stained heart
Exotic knees
One night this is home
She called
Collect to me
I don't love you anymore
She said
May it cease to be
Just a moment
The boy
When I left you
You were young
I was gone
But not my love
You were clearly
Meant for more
Than a life lost
In the war
You were clearly
I wanted to
Be happy
Free to run
Get dizzy on caffeine
Find friends
I'd make you laugh
Maybe you're
Just a little bit
Happy
I
Feel my right
At your side
Don't you know you got my eyes
I'll make you
Fly
You be happy all the time
Oh you can make me
Ride
Boy
Now your life is
Back to front
But you'll see
That's not for long
Cause I know
You'll feel the cold
Over that moon
So low
Oh you know you're not alone
I see you may grow now
For a before and after
We'll be right back.
The corner you love the most
That book you haven't finished reading
Is still sealed away
I've already learned
How to enjoy loneliness
Friends are happy
I'm happy too
The fireworks of the new year
Bloom in the sky
I remember our
Most happy smile
How far I've walked
How many seas I've crossed to see you
In the lonely dark night
As long as I think of you
I won't be confused
Time goes by
People come and go
You don't have to say
I understand
Thank you for letting me
Stay in your eyes
I've already learned
How to enjoy loneliness
Friends are happy
I'm happy too
I've already learned
How to enjoy loneliness
Friends are happy
I'm happy too
I've already learned
How far I've crossed to see you
In the lonely dark night
As long as I think of you, I won't panic
Time flies so fast
You don't have to say you're leaving
I understand
Thank you for letting me stay in your eyes
Timing & subitles brought to you by 中剧独播
Timing & subtitles brought to you by 中剧独播